{
    "id": "833db9f4ddf94218821f4677ecd7822b",
    "title": "As, though and although",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2da9919338f34ccba68413684ea824ed",
            "title": "As, Though And Although",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Hot ………………….. it was, we decided to go out.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "although",
                        "though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………… she was not ready, we went without her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "Though",
                        "Although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Bravely …………………. we fought, we had little chance of winning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "though",
                        "although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………. it might seem, she doesn’t like babies.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though strange",
                        "Strange though",
                        "Strange although",
                        "Although strange"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can’t come and spend the weekend with you, ……………….. I would like to.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as much",
                        "much as",
                        "although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. I didn’t know anybody at the party, I had a nice time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "Although",
                        "As"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………… I was tired, I decided to get some rest.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "Though",
                        "Although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………. I was ill for several months, I lost my job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "Though",
                        "Although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We decided to go out ……………………. it was a bit late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "though",
                        "although",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Lovely evening.’ ‘Yes. Bit cold, …………………’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "though",
                        "although",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}